<!--
  #%L
  LaTeX Track Changes (LTC) allows collaborators on a version-controlled LaTeX writing project to view and query changes in the .tex documents.
  %%
  Copyright (C) 2009 - 2012 SRI International
  %%
  This program is free software: you can redistribute it and/or modify
  it under the terms of the GNU General Public License as
  published by the Free Software Foundation, either version 3 of the 
  License, or (at your option) any later version.
  
  This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful,
  but WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of
  MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.  See the
  GNU General Public License for more details.
  
  You should have received a copy of the GNU General Public 
  License along with this program.  If not, see
  <http://www.gnu.org/licenses/gpl-3.0.html>.
  #L%
  -->
<document xmlns="http://maven.apache.org/changes/1.0.0"
          xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
          xsi:schemaLocation="http://maven.apache.org/changes/1.0.0 http://maven.apache.org/xsd/changes-1.0.0.xsd">
    <properties>
        <title>Changes in LTC</title>
        <author email="lilalinda at users.sourceforge.net">Linda Briesemeister</author>
    </properties>
    <body>
        <release version="1.0" date="2013-April?">

        </release>

        <release version="0.9.14" date="2013-04-10">
            <action dev="lilalinda" type="fix">
                Now parsing non-ASCII characters during lexical analysis.
            </action>
            <action dev="lilalinda" type="fix" issue="21">
                Now parsing natural language constructs for limiting the version control history to a start date.
            </action>
            <action dev="lilalinda" type="update">
                Improved LTC Editor to disable certain GUI controls when presented with an SVN-controlled .tex file,
                as setting "Self" and "Remotes" make no sense in that context.
            </action>
            <action dev="lilalinda" type="add" issue="22">
                Added a boolean setting (persistent) whether to condense authors or not.  By default, this is off so
                we see all intermediate versions of the same author marked up.  The mark up changes once we turn this
                setting on, resulting in skipping intermediate versions (as done in the original implementation).
            </action>
        </release>

        <release version="0.9.13" date="2013-03-19">
            <action dev="lilalinda" type="fix" issue="3">
                LTC Editor now has a button (with shortcut CMD/CTRL-R) to open a dialog to create a bug report.
            </action>
            <action dev="lilalinda" type="fix">
                Install script does not rely on JDK anymore ('jar' tool) to unzip Emacs lisp files.  The documentation
                has been adjusted.
            </action>
            <action dev="lilalinda" type="fix" issue="6">
                About dialog now contains version information but license is only available via command line.  All other
                command line tools have been adjusted to provide a mode of displaying the license.  Small improvements
                to applications under Mac OS X.  When we move to improved deployment (Ubuntu and Mac OS X), we can address
                these things more -- until then issue has been labeled as 'wont-fix'.
            </action>
            <action dev="lilalinda" type="fix" issue="8" due-to="Peter">
                Fixing markup of replacement sentences -- instead of marking up alternating words as replacements, the
                longest subsequence of words is consecutively marked up.
            </action>
            <action dev="lilalinda" type="fix" issue="20">
                Adding revision ID to change markup so that LTC Editor and Emacs mode now display the revision ID with
                each change when the user hovers over a marked up character.
            </action>
        </release>

        <release version="0.9.12" date="2013-01-30">
            <action dev="lilalinda" type="fix" issue="7" due-to="Tomer">
                LTC Server and Editor now runs under Linux again.
            </action>
            <action dev="lilalinda" type="update">
                Emacs mode updates "modified" and "on disk" flags in history as soon as edit and save operations
                happen; revisions and dates are now click-able in history buffer of Emacs mode to use these for
                limiting history; improved menu labels and prompts for user; install script now includes hint how to
                reload the Emacs mode file if Emacs was running while updating
            </action>
            <action dev="lilalinda" due-to="Peter" type="update">
                Better text for home page and link to Peter's web site.
            </action>
            <action dev="lilalinda" due-to="Cher" issue="5" type="update">
                Finalized logo and icon files.
            </action>
        </release>

        <release version="0.9.11" date="2012-12-27">
            <action dev="lilalinda" type="add">
                Adding build information to About dialog, JAR manifest, and bug report.
            </action>
            <action dev="lilalinda" type="update">
                Bug report generation now obeys parameter whether to include the source repository.
            </action>
            <action dev="lilalinda" type="update">
                Emacs mode asks user now whether to include the source repository in bug report;
                it also provides a new command to set an author color without using a mouse-click.
            </action>
        </release>

        <release version="0.9.10" date="2012-12-18" description="first beta-release at sourceforge">
            <action dev="sbreiba" type="add">
                Bug report creation now includes bundles (git) or zip file with file versions (svn).
            </action>
            <action dev="lilalinda" type="update">
                Emacs mode has menu items for bug reports and jumping to next/prev change;
                also added robustness features and better failure messages
            </action>
            <action dev="lilalinda" type="update">
                Fixed coloring of intermediate versions.
            </action>
            <action dev="lilalinda" type="add">
                Added license information, copyright headers etc.
                Moving to hosting at http://latextrack.sourceforge.net.
                New logo and icon for applications.
            </action>
            <action dev="lilalinda" type="add">
                Public SVN repository for testing and tutorial added.
            </action>
            <action dev="lilalinda" type="fix" issue="2">
                Removed command line switch for specifying git binary as this is no longer needed.
            </action>
        </release>

        <release version="0.9.8" date="2012-10-29" description="">
            <action dev="sbreidba" type="add">
                Adding subversion support (the system automatically chooses between git or svn depending on the
                directory where the .tex file is located).
            </action>
            <action dev="sbreidba" type="update">
                More bug fixes for accumulation: still some white space issues.
            </action>
            <action dev="lilalinda" type="update" due-to="sbreidba">
                Started support for bug reports in Emacs (to be continued).
            </action>
            <action dev="lilalinda" type="add">
                Customizable faces for addition and deletion in Emacs mode.
                Jump to next and prev change in Emacs mode.
            </action>
        </release>

        <release version="0.9.7-SNAPSHOT" date="2012-05-30" description="">
            <action dev="lilalinda" type="add">
                Start tracking changes in this project.
            </action>
        </release>
    </body>
</document>